{
    "subject": "resource/A_Lesson_Before_Dying_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/network",
    "object": "resource/HBO",
    "human_readable": "The film A Lesson Before Dying is a part of HBO's network.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.958051860332489,
            "question": "Is 'A Lesson Before Dying' a program on HBO?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9439547657966614,
            "question": "On which network is the film 'A Lesson Before Dying' aired?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8696420192718506,
            "question": "Are there other films available on HBO besides 'A Lesson Before Dying'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.738267183303833,
            "question": "Where can you watch the film 'A Lesson Before Dying'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7283207178115845,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that is part of HBO's network?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7096445560455322,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'A Lesson Before Dying' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4384430944919586,
            "question": "What type of programming is 'A Lesson Before Dying'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32477396726608276,
            "question": "Is HBO known for airing movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2684115469455719,
            "question": "What other types of programs are on HBO besides movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25144755840301514,
            "question": "Is HBO a cable or streaming network?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film A Lesson Before Dying is a part of HBO's network.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6053_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other types of programs are on HBO besides movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6053_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is HBO known for airing movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6053_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of programming is 'A Lesson Before Dying'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6053_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_175.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_180.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_183.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_187.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6053_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that \"A Lesson Before Dying\" was an HBO-produced television drama, supporting the statement that it is part of HBO's network."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}